<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on THOJOTECH</title>
    <link>https://blog.thojotech.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on THOJOTECH</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2022, Joe Thompson; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 10:17:57 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.thojotech.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Use GitHub Actions workflow to deploy your Hugo static website in Azure Storage</title>
      <link>https://blog.thojotech.com/post/hugoazuregithub/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 10:17:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.thojotech.com/post/hugoazuregithub/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            This article is based on Microsoft’s documentation -- Use GitHub Actions workflow to deploy your static website in Azure Storage --, but has been updated to reflect changes required to publish Hugo static sites to Azure blob storage/static web sites. Please see the article linked above for a list of prerequisites.
Generate deployment credentials Using Azure CLI
1$azsubId=&amp;#34;xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx&amp;#34; 2$azStrAcctResourceGroup=&amp;#34;rg-westus2-website&amp;#34; 3$azstorageacct=&amp;#34;stgwestus2webstorageacct&amp;#34; 4az ad sp create-for-rbac --name $azstorageacct --role contributor --scopes /subscriptions/$azsubId/resourceGroups/$azStrAcctResourceGroup --sdk-auth The command will generate a JSON object, copy and save for later:
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Az MySql Flexible-server command returns error</title>
      <link>https://blog.thojotech.com/post/azmysqlflexclierr/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 20:43:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.thojotech.com/post/azmysqlflexclierr/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            I recently started scripting with Azure CLI within my Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) environment and tried to create a database on an Azure Database for MySQL Flexible-Server instance and received an error &#39;flexible-server&#39; is not in the &#39;az mysql&#39; command group. I also tried to list out the flexible-servers in my subscription, but it also give the same error!
I tried to see if maybe my Azure CLI was out of date, but it was already at the newest version!
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes from the field - Microsoft Office 365 Migration</title>
      <link>https://blog.thojotech.com/post/notes-o365/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 09:38:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.thojotech.com/post/notes-o365/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            On a recent Microsoft Office365/Box to OneDrive migration project, I was asked to put together a lessons-learned for the project. Listed below are some of those lessons. The Microsoft Office 365 upgrade project had in scope upgrading users from Office 2010 to O365.
My role: Technical Advisor Company type: Large Hospitality &amp;amp; Gaming
Make sure you have a good sampling of users in the pilot. Office workers, executives, etc.
Inventory is everything.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
